A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Leadership Development Program (LDP), Accession 2017:027 FA1298
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Region-at-Large LDP Fellow files, 1968-1979; 1; 3.3 Cubic Feet About 7.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes
  - A-M, 1968-1979; 1; 2.2 Cubic Feet About 5 LTR size Hollinger Boxes
    - Martinez, Tom - Altus, Oklahoma, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Morgan, Edward B. - Abingdon, Virginia, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, Edward B. - Abingdon, Virginia, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - N-Z, 1968-1977; 2; 1.1 Cubic Feet About 2.5 LTR size Hollinger Boxes
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Region-at-Large Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters N-Z.
    - Paul, Michael M. - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Paul, Michael M. - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Pierre, Steve - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Pierre, Steve - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Prejean, Frederick - Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Prejean, Frederick - Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Pumpkin Seed, Patrick - Wounded Knee, South Dakota, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Pumpkin Seed, Patrick - Wounded Knee, South Dakota, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Ratliff, Mary A. - Racine, West Virginia, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Ratliff, Mary A. - Racine, West Virginia, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Robertson, Dorothy Jean - Caruthersville, Missouri, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Robertson, Dorothy Jean - Caruthersville, Missouri, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Russell, Bertha M. - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      LDP Fellow, short-term award: 1969
    - Russell, Bertha M. - Spokane, Washington, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Slonaker, Steve - Capon Bridge, West Virginia, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Slonaker, Steve - Capon Bridge, West Virginia, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Spearman, John - Lawrence, Kanas, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Spearman, John - Lawrence, Kansas, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - St. Clair, Chester - Fort Washakie, Wyoming, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - St. Clair, Chester - Fort Washakie, Wyoming, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - St. John, Dan and Regina - St. Paul Island, Alaska, 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 89-91)
    - St. John, Dan and Regina - St. Paul Island, Alaska, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Taylor, Frank - Wise, Virginia, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Teeluk, Martha - Fairbanks, Alaska, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Teeluk, Martha - Fairbanks, Alaska, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Timm, Verl - Haxtun, Colorado, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 96-97)
      2. Reports
    - Townes, Gus, Jr. - Hayti, Missouri, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Townes, Gus, Jr. - Hayti, Missouri, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Watts, Roy L. - Baxter, Tennessee, 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Watts, Roy L. - Baxter, Tennessee, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - White Magpie, Melvin - Boise, Idaho, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - White Magpie, Melvin - Boise, Idaho, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Whitman, Silas - Lapwai, Idaho, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Whitman, Silas - Lapwai, Idaho, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Wolfe, Henry, Jr. - Laplace, Louisiana, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Wolfe, Henry, Jr. - Laplace, Louisiana, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Worthington, William - Coxton, Kentucky, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Wright, Erle C., Jr. - Wise, Virginia, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Wright, Erle C., Jr. - Wise, Virginia, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Zamora, Alfredo - Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Zamora, Alfredo - Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 112)
- Northeast Region LDP Fellow files, 1966-1977; 2; 7.72 Cubic Feet About 17 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger box
  The series consists entirely of Fellow files for the Leadership Development Program Northeast Region Office. For the most part, these files follow the general organizational scheme imposed by the records' creators for all Fellow files documenting the LDP. This means that most Northeast Region Fellows have two files for their associated records: One file holding original narrative reports submitted to Northeast Regional Representative/Program Consultant Paul Judkins by the individual Fellow and one file holding narrative report copies submitted to the Ford Foundation by Judkins' office. The Northeast Region files are also comprised of the same type of content as the rest of the Fellow files found within the collection. In addition to narrative reports, they chiefly contain correspondence between Judkins and individual Fellows, correspondence between Judkins and Ford LDP staff, and correspondence between Judkins and organizations that provided internships and other learning opportunities to LDP Fellows. Correspondence generally regards submissions of reports, fellowship progress, fellowship changes, and post fellowship activities.
  The LDP Northeast Region Selection Committee recruited Fellows from the states of Maine, New Hampshire, and Vermont as well as from the New Brunswick Province of Canada. Judkin's Office kept fellowship application documents and Fellow evaluation reports within many of the Fellow files.
  Northeast Region LDP Fellows generally focused on the areas of education, psychology, and guidance counseling. Records contained within the various Fellow files provide evidence that many Fellows sought to improve public education through the refinement and implementation of innovative teaching styles such as individualized instruction as well as through the reimagining of course curricula. The topic of humanities studies and humanistic education appears throughout many of the files. Fellows designed their program years around such specific education subjects as bilingual education, environmental education, sex education, and recreational programs. A particularly large number of files consists of records concerning special education services. The intended recipients of these services varied between students with physical disabilities, learning disabilities, mental disabilities, and emotional disabilities.
  Materials related to special education services also appear within the files of those Fellows who pursued psychology-focused program years. Child development and mental health are other prominent subjects within those Fellows' files. Lastly, documents related to career development and vocational training can be found within the records of those Fellows who emphasized guidance counseling in their program and post-fellowship activities.
  African Americans and Native Americans were the two most prominent minority groups served by Northeast Region LDP Fellows.
  In addition to correspondence and reports, the series holds pamphlets, newsletters, press clippings, papers, publications, and postcards.
  This series was broken into four subseries during processing in order to improve user access to the large number of files produced by the Northeast Region Office.
  Series 2 Subseries 1. A-F, 1966-1976
  Series 2 Subseries 2. G-M, 1966-1976
  Series 2 Subseries 3. N-S, 1967-1977
  Series 2 Subseries 4. T-Z, 1967-1975
  - A-F, 1966-1976; 1; 2.64 Cubic Feet About 6 LTR size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Northeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters A-F.
    - Allaby, Eric - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Allaby, Eric - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Albert, Louis P. - Maine, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 115)
      LDP Fellow, short-term award: 1968
    - Arnott, William III - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Arnott, William III - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Babin, Patrick - Maine, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 118-120)
      LDP Fellow: 1967-1968
    - Badwey, Carol - Vermont, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Badwey, Carol - Vermont, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Bainton, Ernest - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Bainton, Ernest - New Hampshire, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Battiste, Tom - Maine, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Battiste, Tom - Maine, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Battiste, Tom - Maine, circa 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 127)
      Original folder was empty of content.
    - Begley, Charles M. - Maine, 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Belanger, Shirley - New Hampshire, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Bennett, Dean - Maine, 1967-1976 (Box 10, Folder 130-131)
    - Bernard, Peter - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Bernard, Peter - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Billard, Richard - Vermont, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Boudreau, Andre - New Brunswick, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Boudreau, Andre - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 136-137)
    - Bowie, Gordon - Maine, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Bowie, Gordon - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Burbank, Thomas H. - New Hampshire, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Calder, John - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Calder, John - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Carroll, Robert J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Carroll, Robert J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Chaplin, Robert - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Chaplin, Robert - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Chase, David A. - Maine, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 147)
      LDP Fellow, short-term award: 1967
    - Chase, David A. - Maine, 1966-1972 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Chater, Marna - Vermont, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Childs, William F. - New Hampshire, 1967-1974 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Clendening, Gary F. - Maine, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Colcord, Charles - New Hampshire, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Cole, Charles - Vermont, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Cote, Bernard - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Cote, Bernard - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Cowan, Joan L. - Vermont, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 156)
    - Cowan, Joan L. - Vermont, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 157-158)
    - Crosby, Elaine - Maine, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Crosby, Elaine - Maine, 1970-1975 (Box 12, Folder 160-161)
    - Dale, Walter - New Hampshire, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 162-163)
    - Dale, Walter - New Hampshire, 1968-1974 (Box 12, Folder 164-166)
    - Davis, Roger - Maine, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - DeForge, Nancy - Vermont, 1968-1974 (Box 13, Folder 168)
      Within the file, materials refer to Leadership Development Program Fellow Nancy DeForge by several different names including Nancy Deforge, Nancy Hollenbeck (DeForge's maiden name), and Mrs. Wayne Deforge.
    - DePaul, Pearl - Vermont, 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Diamond, William - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - DiLego, Pasquale - Vermont, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - DiLego, Pasquale - Vermont, 1969-1974 (Box 13, Folder 172)
      A still image titled Sedimentation Project has been removed from the file for stabilization.
    - Dotson (nee Austin), Judith - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 173-174)
    - Dotson (nee Austin), Judith - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 175-176)
      A set of still images titled Jonathon Dotson Personalized Postcards has been removed from the file (folder 176) for stabilization.
    - Douglass, Dale - Maine, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 177)
      LDP Fellow, short-term award: 1970
    - Douglass, Dale - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Dumont, Wilfred - Maine, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Dumont, Wilfred - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Edwards, Ellen - Vermont, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Elliott, June - Vermont, 1968-1974 (Box 14, Folder 182-183)
    - Ellis, J. William, Jr. - New Hampshire, 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Emerson, Jon H. - Vermont, 1967-1974 (Box 14, Folder 185-186)
    - Fogarty, Patrick - Maine, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Fogarty, Patrick - Maine, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Francis, Deanna - Maine, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Francis, George J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 190-191)
    - Francis, George J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - G-M, 1966-1976; 2; 2 Cubic Feet About 4.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Northeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters G-M.
    - Goulet, Irene - New Hampshire, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Goulet, Irene - New Hampshire, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Gray, Kenneth - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Gray, Kenneth - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Griffin, Conrad - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Griffin, Conrad - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Griggs, Eleanor - Vermont, 1971-1976 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Grover (nee Boynton), Alice - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Hagner, William - Vermont, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Hagner, William - Vermont, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Hale, Frances - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - Hale, Frances - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 204-205)
      Within the original folder, another folder labeled "Project Maine Stream, Paul Judkins, Jr." had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Haskins, Harold J. - New Hampshire, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Hastings, Scott E., Jr. - Vermont, 1967-1975 (Box 16, Folder 207-208)
    - Hawley, Paul - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Hawley, Paul - New Hampshire, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Hayes, Philip - Maine, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - Hayes, Philip - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 212-213)
    - Hazlett, James - Vermont, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Hazlett, James - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Hedgepeth, Joseph - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Hedgepeth, Joseph - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Helson, Christina - Maine, 1968-1973 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Howe, Robert J. - Vermont, 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 219)
    - Hutchins, Lewis - Maine, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 220)
    - Hutchins, Lewis - Maine, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 221)
    - Jones, Lois - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - Jones, Lois - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - Jones, Lois - Maine, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 224)
    - Jones, Robert A. - Maine, 1967-1974 (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Justice, Thomas R. - New Hampshire, 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Keeser, Ellen - New Hampshire, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - Keeser, Ellen - New Hampshire, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Kenaston, Richard - Maine, 1968-1974 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Lamrock, F. Leonard - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - Lamrock, F. Leonard - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 231)
      =
    - Laramie, Spencer - New Hampshire, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 232-233)
    - Lauman, Vern - Vermont, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - Lauman, Vern - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - Lawton, Edward - New Hampshire, 1968-1975 (Box 18, Folder 236)
    - Lebrun, Sister Marguerite - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - Lebrun, Sister Marguerite - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Leister, Robert - Vermont, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Leister, Robert - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 240-241)
      An audio recording titled Leister to Judkins has been removed from the file (folder 240) for stabilization.
    - Lindsey, Nancy Jane - New Hampshire, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 242-243)
    - MacDougall, Walter M. - Maine, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 244)
    - McCrillis, Dean A. - Maine, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 245)
    - Toomey, Sister Bernard Michele - Vermont, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 246)
    - Mills, Bertram V. - New Hampshire, 1967-1975 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - N-S, 1967-1977; 3; 2.2 Cubic Feet About 5 LTR size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Northeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters N-S.
    - Nay, John B. - New Hampshire, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 248)
    - Nay, John B. - New Hampshire, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 249-250)
    - Newell, Wayne - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 251)
    - Newell, Wayne - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 252)
    - Noyes, Harold H. - Maine, 1967-1971 (Box 20, Folder 253)
    - O'Brien, Sister Mary Paschal - Maine, 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 254)
    - Patterson, Wayne - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 255)
    - Patterson, Wayne - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 256)
    - Paul, Cecilia - New Brunswick, Canada, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 257)
    - Paul, Cecilia - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 258)
    - Paul, William - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 259)
    - Paul, William - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 260)
    - Pelletier, Bernard - Maine, 1967-1974 (Box 20, Folder 261)
    - Penner, William J. - Vermont, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 262)
    - Perley, Donald P. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 263)
    - Perley, Donald P. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - Perley, Marjorie and Aubrey - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 265)
    - Perley, Marjorie and Aubrey - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - Perry, Marion - Vermont, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 267)
    - Perry, Marion - Vermont, 1969-1975 (Box 21, Folder 268)
    - Pinette, James - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 269)
    - Pinette, James - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 270)
    - Plourde, Sister Paula - Maine, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 271)
    - Plummer, Gary - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 272)
    - Plummer, Gary - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 273)
    - Polchies, Terrance - Maine, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 274)
    - Prue, Martha - Vermont, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 275)
    - Prue, Martha - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - Punt, Glendon - Vermont, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 277)
    - Punt, Glendon - Vermont, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 278)
    - Ragle, Barbara - Vermont, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 279)
    - Ramsay, Laura Ann - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 280)
      Within the file, materials refer to Leadership Development Program Fellow Laura Ann Ramsay as both Laura Ann Ramsay and Ann Ramsay.
    - Ramsay, Laura Ann - New Hampshire, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 281)
    - Ranslow, Stephen G. - Maine, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 282)
    - Ranslow, Stephen G. - Maine, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 283-284)
    - Richards, Peter - Vermont, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 285)
    - Richards, Peter - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 286)
    - Richardson, Katherine - Vermont, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 287)
    - Richardson, Katherine - Vermont, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 288)
    - Richardson, Sheldon - Maine, 1967-1975 (Box 22, Folder 289-290)
    - Riel, Sister Rita - Maine, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - Riel, Sister Rita - Maine, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 292-293)
      Original folder subheadings include
    - Robinson, Donald - Vermont, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 294)
    - Robinson, Donald - Vermont, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 295-296)
    - Rosenblum, Marvin - Maine, 1968-1974 (Box 23, Folder 297-298)
    - Ryan, Bruce G.- New Hampshire, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - Sappier, James - Maine, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 300)
    - Sappier, James - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 301)
    - Sarty, Meryl - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 302)
    - Sarty, Meryl - New Brunswick, Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 303)
    - Savage, William - New Hampshire, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 304)
    - Settle, Wayne - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 305)
    - Settle, Wayne - Maine, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 306)
    - Sewell, Gilbert - New Brunswick, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 307)
    - Sharp, Kathleen - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 308)
    - Sharp, Kathleen - New Hampshire, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 309-310)
    - Sher, Jonathan Paul - Vermont, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 311)
    - Slauenwhite, Bradley J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 312)
    - Slauenwhite, Bradley J.- New Brunswick, Canada, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - Smit, Martin - Vermont, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - Smit, Martin - Vermont, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 315)
    - Somers, Melvin C. - Vermont, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 316)
    - Stackelberg, Roderick - Vermont, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 317)
    - Stackelberg, Roderick - Vermont, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 318)
    - Stearns, Beverly - Vermont, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 319)
    - Stearns, Beverly - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 320)
  - T-Z, 1967-1975; 4; .88 Cubic Feet About 1.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger box
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Northeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters T-Z.
    - Taylor, Kenneth O. - New Hampshire, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 321)
    - Theriault, Father Leo - New Brunswick, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 322)
    - Theriault, Father Leo - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 323)
    - Thompson, Eugenia - Maine, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 324)
    - Thompson, Eugenia - Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 325)
    - Tillotson, Patricia - New Hampshire, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 326)
    - Tillotson, Patricia - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 327)
    - Tyczynski, Edward J. - New Brunswick, Canada, 1967-1975 (Box 25, Folder 328)
    - Verret, Pierrette - New Brunswick, Canada, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 329)
    - Verret, Pierrette - New Brunswick, Canada, circa 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 330)
      File was missing from original box.
    - Vincent, Harold - Vermont, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 331)
    - Vincent, Harold - Vermont, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 332)
    - Walker, Margot - New Hampshire, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 333)
    - Walker, Margot - New Hampshire, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 334)
    - Wells, Duane S. - Vermont, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 335)
    - Whipple, Mary Jane - New Brunswick, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 336)
    - Whitaker, Daniel J. - New Hampshire, 1968-1974 (Box 25, Folder 337)
    - White, Nancy A. - New Hampshire, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 338)
    - Whitten, Jere - Maine, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    - Whitten, Jere - Maine, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - Wiggett, Henry - Vermont, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 341)
    - Wiggett, Henry - Vermont, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 342)
    - Williamson, Andrew, III - Maine, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 343)
    - Williamson, Andrew, III - Maine, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 344)
    - Wilson, Lee S. - Vermont, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 345)
    - Wood, George, Jr. - Vermont, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 346)
    - Worthley, Leon - New Hampshire, circa 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 347)
      LDP Fellow: nominated 1971-1972, postponed 1972-1973
    - Worthley, Leon - New Hampshire, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 348)
    - Worthley, Leon - New Hampshire, 1970-1974 (Box 26, Folder 349)
- Southwest Region LDP Fellow files, 1967-1980; 3; 7.84 Cubic Feet About 16.75 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 1 LGL size Hollinger box